const Der = 'der';
const Die = 'die';
const Das = 'das';
const Den = 'den';
const Dem = 'dem';
const Des = 'des';

const DefiniteArticles = [Der, Die, Das, Den, Dem, Des];

const ArticleCards = [
    {
        question: 'What is the nominative masculine article?',
        answer: Der,
        options: DefiniteArticles
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the nominative feminine article?',
        answer: Die,
        options: DefiniteArticles
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the nominative neuter article?',
        answer: Das,
        options: DefiniteArticles
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the nominative plural article?',
        answer: Die,
        options: DefiniteArticles
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the accusative masculine article?',
        answer: Den,
        options: DefiniteArticles
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the accusative feminine article?',
        answer: Die,
        options: DefiniteArticles
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the accusative neuter article?',
        answer: Das,
        options: DefiniteArticles
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the accusative plural article?',
        answer: Die,
        options: DefiniteArticles
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the dative masculine article?',
        answer: Dem,
        options: DefiniteArticles
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the dative feminine article?',
        answer: Der,
        options: DefiniteArticles
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the dative neuter article?',
        answer: Dem,
        options: DefiniteArticles
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the dative plural article?',
        answer: Den,
        options: DefiniteArticles
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the genitive masculine article?',
        answer: Des,
        options: DefiniteArticles
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the genitive feminine article?',
        answer: Der,
        options: DefiniteArticles
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the genitive neuter article?',
        answer: Des,
        options: DefiniteArticles
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the genetive plural article?',
        answer: Der,
        options: DefiniteArticles
    }
];

export default ArticleCards;